be 20-year-old.
You see these $1,000? Well, I'm going to
help him flip this into $100,000. And
his name is David, or also known as the
GK Kid, where he was hand selected from
50,000 people that applied to be in this
position. And after reviewing 50,000
applications, flying to multiple
different states, and after interviewing
15 different people in person, we're
left with David. He came in as David,
but he's going to be leaving as the
chief. Well, that's what I thought, but
we ended up blowing the account. So, the
challenge started off pretty early. I
think it started off around 8:00 in the
morning. We ended up taking GBP CAD,
which was a decent trade. was a bit
premature in my opinion. But the most
important thing about this trade was
that we risked 100% of it on the first
go because the first trade has to be a
home run. And these account flips, it's
extremely essential that you risk 100%
on the first trade because it's the only
one that's going to get you out of the
hole and then you can minimize your risk
as you go. The first trade is the most
important. So, we're about to take our
first trade right now and I was just
telling David that, bro, let me take the
first trade. Trust me, it's the most
important trade
>> and we're going to risk 100% right now.
Like like this trade is going to make or
break the whole entire account right
now. [__] it. [__] it. All right. So,
we're going to enter GP CAD after this
shift of structure. The 1 hour time
frame is a shift of structure. And now
we are having that wick retracement. All
right. Let's enter. Just to show you
guys, $1,000 GP CAD trade. And then not
90 lots and $1,000. That would be crazy.
We're going to start off with let's just
put two lots and stop loss is going to
be 1.85733.
1.85733
and All right. So, we want you you can
click the sub button.
>> Okay.
>> Tell sell.
>> Now, this is a trade that I've
personally taken over 600 700 times over
my career. And I've been expressing to
David the risk of this type of trade.
And obviously, I've made a lot of money
with this type of style, but I've also
lost a lot of money with this type of
style. And little did we know what was
right ahead of us was going to basically
bite us right in the ass. David was
about to experience his first diddy.
>> What's up? So, how does it feel like to
be a week into the house? Crazy. I mean,
I've changed so much stuff in my life
and learned so much stuff as well. So,
what was everything you learned last
week?
>> Uh, basically I learned like I already
knew about the trading. Uh, Alex
basically reinforced that knowledge. And
another goal Alex put for you was for
you to lose weight. So, how much are you
weighing now and how much do you think
you're going to weigh at the end? When
Alex told me to lose weight, I didn't
know it was going to be harder, the
traits or the weight part. And mind you,
Alex had me not eating, doing sauna
three times a day and a lot of cardio.
When I landed, I was in 236. Right now,
I'm on 227. And by the end of the
challenge, hopefully 200 200 two 200
210.
>> Yo,
>> hold up. Hold up real quick. Update.
>> Okay, I got you. I got you.
>> Great update. So, and when I called you,
we're actually up 9. Like the highest
we've been was 950.
>> 950 already.
>> I know. I know. So, at the start of the
trade, me and David were already
celebrating our first win before even
closing the trade. We even saw highs of
I think over $900. And truthfully, that
was already almost 100% of our account.
And to many that might be a lot, but our
goal for the week was $3,000. So, we had
to make sure that we continued to hold
that position. And to David, that's the
fastest he's ever seen that type of
money be made. And he wanted to close
right off the bat. But I could have
explained to him it's not about the
money, it's about the percentage. We
need to 3x the account so we can triple
up every single week and finish the
challenge in under a month. Or that's at
least the goal. So we have to stick to
the plan and set and forget. We only
close out the trade if it hits our
takerit for a minimum of a 1 to 2.5 risk
reward to upwards of a 1 to three.
That's how you properly do an account
flip. You can't just close it because
you see lots of dollar amounts on the
balance. No, you need to have a positive
risk-to-reward road ratio, which to me
personally is anything above a 1 to 2.5.
So right here, you can see the left
head, right shoulder. Technically, we
broke the neckline. We retested that
structure point and now we're having the
continuation to the downside. So look,
right now we're up 800 bucks.
>> I can't believe we blew the account.
>> I am not market update. Right now, it is
currently 10:00 at night. We have
officially blown the account. We have
lost GBP CAD and we lost GBP CAD because
of [__] [__] wick out broke. So
GBP CAD we were in this cell earlier. So
after the 30 minute had this head and
shoulder shift structure. We then had to
pull back up into this area. We rejected
from it. This is where we at the range
and it did a little bit but um not
enough. This this is like real [__]
Like this is for real [__] This is
how you know they're watching us. It
literally went direct to my stop loss
and as soon as it went to my stop loss,
direct into profit. So, this is
literally showing you that they're
watching us.
>> And we first blew up the account. I
thought it was over. I thought Alex were
going to send me home. Now, this could
have not honestly happened any more
perfect. The fact that this happened on
the first trade that we got wicked out
by what was it? Four pips, five pips. I
think it was a perfect example of what
this challenge has set the standard for
from the beginning forward. letting us
know that this is not going to be easy
and that the markets are not going to
give us easy trades to make this
account. The market was going to
challenge us. The markets was going to
beat us up and we were ready for that
challenge because I'm telling you right
now, this could have not been a worse
start to the challenge. And that right
there was truthfully one of the best
lessons that I could have asked the
market to give David. And that is do not
enter a trade too early. Make sure your
stop-loss placement is at a point where
if it gets hit, you're completely wrong.
And most importantly, that these account
flips are extremely high risk. That you
need to be extremely aware of every
single position you're going to be
entering and how much you're going to
risk because in a heartbeat like that,
you can completely blow your whole
entire account. This is not a way of how
to consistently make profits in the
market. These are just fun account flip
challenges that I personally like to do
because trading gets boring over time.
And this is stuff that just makes me
more of a precise trader. Makes it just
tests my skills. And I want to make that
very clear to David right at the start
because truthfully, you don't want to
normalize this type of trading. So, what
do we do after we blow the account? What
do you think? We're going to just stop
and not continue to go. No. Like, this
is what happens when you do account
flips. You're prone to blowing the
account. So, we just deposited another
$1,000 and got right back up. We went
again right at it.
>> But it's fine. It's fine.
>> No big deal.
>> We're not going to get nervous.
>> No, no. We got another $1,000 in us
>> already. Yeah. We're going to use your
money now.
>> Okay, cool.
But we made another mistake.
>> [__] man.
>> This is your fault. My fault.
>> Yeah.
>> Why? You didn't wake me up.
>> And that was my first time having to
wake up to trade at night. I didn't know
I was a thing.
>> So, we got wicked out. So, those guys
with the hats, bro, they wicked us out
after that. Gave us the perfect
engulfing. And then what happened?
Exactly what I said. Straight to our
takerit. If I would have literally just
woken up for 30 seconds. I would have
just taken it from my phone. Just taken
it right there in that spot.
>> No. The worst part is like imagine if we
would have just not been wicked out at
the point that we would be right now.
>> No. No. Right. Right now, right now the
account would be at $4,000.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh no. And at this point, I believe that
the market is actually doing this on
purpose. I believe that the market is
watching us do this challenge because it
is giving us the most perfect lessons
that anybody can ask for if they're
starting trading, which is proper
stop-loss placement, getting wicked out,
and then this sticking to your plan.
Here, what did we do? We fell asleep. We
didn't stick to our plan and we didn't
wake up in London session after getting
wicked out and we missed out on the
whole entire trade. Yeah, that sucks. I
rather take a full-blown loss and be
wrong about the trade then get diddied
and then the trade goes straight to take
profit. Like that is the worst. So yes,
if we would have stayed awake or gotten
up at night and we would have entered
the same trade again at the exact same
point, we would have been north of
$3,000. basically hitting our goal for
the week on the exact same trade that we
would have taken or that we actually
already took. Now, does it suck that we
missed the first trade and we would have
been at the goal for the week? Yes. But
that's the beauty of the market that the
market is going to give you another
opportunity. And that's exactly what we
ended up taking. We ended up taking AUD
CAD, which was another little bit of a
higher risk trade. But truthfully, at
the point that we are in the challenge
now, this is the moment to take the
risk. We got to get out of the hole. We
got to make sure this is the trade
that's going to give us the goal of
$3,000 so we can hit the goal for the
week and then next week we continue to
push forward. You know what this is
called?
>> [__] it way.
>> No, it's called revenge trading.
>> Oh yeah,
>> this is how you really make money.
>> You really make money in revenge
trading. All right, so this next trade
that we're going to take right now is
AUD CAD. AUD CAD. Right now we're having
a rejection from the area of interest.
Daily time frame is potentially creating
a daily wick or a dogee. The 1 hour is
creating a little head and shoulders
pattern. So, we have left head, right
shoulder. We have an engulfing evening
star formation here. 30 minute. If we
body candlestick close below this
candlestick right here, I'm going to
immediately enter that trade. So, we're
going to we're going to go for AUD cat.
Dude, that's exact.
>> [__] [__] Look, look. You can't make
this [__] up, man.
>> You can't make this [__] up. Literally,
give us the [__] thing right now.
Click it again. Click it again. Sell
sell. You almost clicked by sell. I was
going there.
>> Two lots. Sell, sell, sell. Wait, wait.
The stop loss. Sell. Sell.
>> There you go.
>> Let me click this one. 5 0 one sell.
>> Boom. Teamwork. There you go.
>> Yeah. So, this is a take profit. We
should be around $3,000. So, we entered
the trade.
>> I feel a lot better now.
>> You feel
>> All right. So, AUD CAD sell. We are in
right now. We're going to just continue
to hold this position and we're going to
completely ignore the [__] fact that
GBP CAD could have easily given us.
>> Look, even more.
>> Yeah. Literally. No. No. This shit's
going to keep going down, bro. Like,
it's going to keep plummeting to the
downside, bro. Whatever. All right.
Settle for Oh [__] Get him. Get him.
So, even though this trade was decently
moving into profit and it was looking
promising, we can't forget the fact that
we just took a loss and we broke our
trading plan and we missed out on
profit. We broke our rules. So,
something that I'm very big on is
holding myself accountable for whenever
I do something wrong. And I had to make
sure that I create this system and this
mindset into David because if you do not
hold yourself accountable, nobody else
is. Only you are going to know when you
make a mistake and you are going to be
the only one that knows if you correct
yourself and hold yourself accountable.
If not, who is? And if you don't start
doing that, you start getting sloppy and
it's just not a good look. If at this
level in my career, I'm still doing it.
So should David. We got to hold
ourselves accountable for the mistakes
that I did. I made a mistake by falling
asleep last night. Have you heard of The
Punisher?
>> The Punisher. The the show.
>> You don't know what The Punisher is?
>> I know. I know what a punish is, but I
don't know what The Punisher.
>> Well, I have something called The
Punisher.
>> Okay. Okay. So, it's it's a you thing.
>> Yeah. It's it's an us thing now.
>> Us US us thing now.
>> So, whenever I do something wrong, we
both pay the price.
>> Okay. What's the price that we have to
pay?
>> Welcome.
>> I know. I think it's been 6 months since
I turned on the Punisher. This is what
we got, brother. Oh, this is what I got.
But we're both paying the price for not
waking up last night. All right. All
right. So, you're sweating already.
>> Yeah. So, you're understanding how this
just sucks. It does indeed. We could be
in a Rolls-Royce right now or a Bugatti,
but we're in here. And that's okay.
There will be better days. We learn from
our mistakes.
>> Set and forget. That's right.
>> And like I've been saying, I truly
believe that the market is watching us
and is doing everything against us
because we were literally 23 24 $2500 in
profit almost at the goal for the week.
And I decided to stick to the plan,
continue to set and forget because
that's what led me to success. And what
happened? The market came back and
margin called us and closed one of our
positions. We go from being almost at
the goal for the week in floating profit
to then at the point where we get our
positions closed.
Yeah, that sucks. This is turning into
some [__] right now, bro. For real.
Like, I'm not even mad anymore. I'm not
even going to This is some [__] So,
we literally just got margin called
right now.
>> The first position,
>> bro. So, our first position, AUD CAD,
just got margin called and I wish we
would have caught it live. Literally, it
happened 2 minutes ago. But basically,
price just had this ridiculous pullback.
So, look at this. We have the left
headed, right shoulder. Yesterday, we
had the strong break as we're playing
basketball. We're literally down here.
And I anticipated a quick retest of this
area. And I was actually interested in
adding a position right now to sell, but
I said, you know what, let me wait.
because I saw that there was news
happening today at 8:30 in the morning
with USD, but I did not think it was
going to affect AUD CAD. I did not think
it was going to create such a massive
move like this on this market. And
clearly it [__] did for whatever
reason. And now we have pretty much
blown the account again.
>> Like I mean it could still technically
reject that area. And now some of you
guys are going to ask, "Oh, why don't
you guys go break even?" Well, we never
go break even. You already know that
breaking even is like us not being okay
with losing. We're totally okay with
losing and
>> part of the learning.
>> It's it's literally part of the process.
But [__] bro. We were literally
>> yesterday we were up 1,000 and
something.
>> Almost like 1,200,300.
>> So the Marcus tried to didd us again.
It's like if Diddy's watching every
single one of our moves. Honestly, at
this point, I was ready to get Diddi
again. But working with Alex side by
side helped me understand and react way
way faster to the market changes.
>> And I said, you know what? We're not
going to let this get to us. We've been
here before. What happened last time
that we got diddy and we got wicked out.
We were right about the move, but we
just happened to have the wrong stop
loss. The market kept going in our
direction. We had just seen this happen
in the last trade. So, what did we do in
this exact same trade? Well, we decided
to not sit on the sidelines. We had just
held oursel accountable by making that
mistake and we decided to enter the
trade right back again. And guess what?
It paid off. learning from literally
right as our last lesson. We are
literally profiting from it right after
that. This is the beauty of the market.
You can make a mistake and capitalize
off of it right after in the next market
move. We're up about 400 bucks. So,
we're technically up we're at break even
right now. So, you can see right here
from the market that we are currently
having a very strong rejection from this
area after we created the major
liquidity grab. So, this is literally
literally just like a
>> new thing,
>> bro. It's it's not even that. It's just
literally them just taking the money.
The point is that right now we are
around break even of the account. I was
actually going to deposit an extra 300
bucks to then enter the trade with more
risk, but I said, you know what, let's
just enter it here. We're going to
continue to set and forget today.
There's nothing else that we can do. If
the trade makes it all the way down
here, which I do anticipate that it
could, we should be up around like 2500
3,000 in the account. And I feel like it
almost happened instantly. We went from
being about $688
in the balance to being upwards of
$1,500 in profit. Now, for all the real
OGs that followed the challenge live the
whole entire step of the way, you guys
know that we didn't take a,000 to
100,000. We technically took $688
or 600 and change to the 100,000 because
we never ended up depositing more money
in after we got margin called on those
positions. Just a little reminder for
those that were watching the challenge
and for people that just aren't aware.
We actually ended up completing the
challenge not with $1,000 but with 600
and change. So everything from this
point forward was pretty much just
constant trade updates. Trade updates
trade updates up 500 up a,000 up 1500
minus 1,000 plus,800. It just kept going
up and down throughout this whole entire
time. So after these endless
takeprofits, something finally happened.
The market literally had just gotten
into my take-profit zone and I happened
to not be home that night. I happened to
be at a barbecue with my friends and I
got the notification on my phone that
the trade had hit take profit, but we
hadn't closed it just yet. So, I asked
my friends to hold the camera and that
we're going to do a live trade update on
that spot and we're going to close the
position right there. We're going to
close all the positions live right now
for 2,300. Close right here. All the
positions live. Going close all
positions. Boom. Trade update closed.
>> David wasn't there. I think he was home
sleeping or something, but we ended up
closing in profit at the barbecue. I
would have loved to do it with David,
but just wasn't there.
>> I didn't go anybody to the barbecue
anyways.
>> So, the goal for the challenge for that
week was 3,000 and I think we were at
2,300 and change, but we wanted to reach
that $3,000 goal so we can continue to
scale. And after already seeing how the
other markets had moved where we would
have been up 5,000 on the first GBP CAD,
up another 5,000 on the other GBP CAD,
we would have been up about 15 $12,000
if we would have also entered AUD CAD on
top of that, risking about 50% of the
account, not even 100%. So all of that
got me to like damn we have just
predicted four out of four markets and
we barely caught one and we're barely at
the takerit for the goal of the week.
So, we might need to find another
opportunity. So, we did see another
decent market opportunity, and I gave
David very clear instructions. All you
got to do is stay awake. I'm tired. All
you got to do is if this market gives me
this engulfing candlestick, you call me.
We'll record it. We take the trade.
Everything will be good. And for some
reason, I felt like he was not going to
be awake. So I decided to be awake for
myself just in case that the market gave
us that opportunity. And guess what? The
Marcus gave us that opportunity. And
guess what? David did not wake up. So we
had to teach him another lesson. A small
rude awakening. What would you rather
have? A leaf blower wake you up or
nightmares of you missing out on a trade
wake you up? I'll pick the leaf blower
all day. Market update right now 2:16 in
the morning and would you look at that?
No missed calls. David
lot of weight.
>> Where's David? Guess what happened?
David didn't [__] wake up and this is
going to cost nonetheless. Big market
did exactly as I said. Right now we are
up about 1,700 bucks. So almost 100% of
what we decided to take. So market trade
update. We had price pull up to this
area. We got a ginormous dogee rejection
candle. This took exactly what I wanted
for us to enter the trade. So, David was
supposed to call me at 1 in the morning
to take this trade. Guess what? He
didn't. I was taking a shower at that
time and I saw the trade close like
that. I took the trade immediately and
waited for his call. But he never woke
up. He would have missed out on this
opportunity.
What happened, bro?
>> You were supposed to wake up from
London, brother.
>> And that could be easily top one worst
ways that I've been woken up before. So,
the next market update in the morning, I
think we're up about $2,000, which was
almost $4,000 total for the accounts to
be in profit, making us being over the
actual goal for the week, which was
phenomenal. But the trade hadn't hit
take profit just yet. And by a hair, we
almost missed out on this opportunity
because if I decided to not stay awake,
we would have completely missed out on
it because David was not waking up. And
at this point, I would have thought that
the market has taught David a lot of
lessons. But it still somehow finds a
way to teach me a lesson. And that is
because we had to completely disqualify
this last trade. We had to withdraw the
profits that we made from GBPNZD because
we did not send that out in the WhatsApp
and Telegram. And the way this challenge
works is every single trade that I take
inside of the challenge, I have to share
with you guys completely for free. If I
don't share it, I cannot take the trade.
So, I woke up David with a leaf blower
for no reason. I stayed up for no reason
and we had to withdraw the profits that
we made on this trade simply because I
did not send GVPND as a trade idea
inside of the WhatsApp and Telegram
where we were sharing the before, the
during, and the after of every single
trade as we're doing the whole entire
challenge. Does that suck? Yes, because
I did record it for YouTube and I did
record it for I believe it was my
Instagram story, but I didn't record it
for the Telegram and WhatsApp channel.
So, too much recording, lack of sleep.
Uh just a lot everything got combined. I
forgot one communications channel of it.
I can't have that in my conscious. Could
I have slid it under the rug and made an
excuse about it and made it make sense?
Sure. But I couldn't carry that on my
conscious that I was not being 100% to
my word. So we just withdrew the profits
and pretended like it never happened. So
at this point in the challenge, we have
been diddied nearly two times. We have
missed out on another two opportunities.
And the one trade that we do take, guess
what? We disqualified. Like the market
is just beating us up at this point. And
it's only the first week. And now after
this point, you would expect that after
many of these market opportunities being
extremely volatile that the market would
keep going and especially after you just
got diddi missed out on positions and
you cannot count a trade. The last thing
you want to do is not take a trade and
do anything. Well, that's exactly what
we did. Me and David stayed awake all
night looking at the computer screen and
at each other for no reason. There was
no trades at all. And even though we
technically did not end off the week
where we wanted to, even though we had
all the opportunities to do that, we
still ended up in profit. We were still
technically up on the challenge for the
week. We didn't hit our goal. We were
shy of it by a couple hundred, but we
did everything correctly. We held oursel
accountable. We learned from our
lessons. And most importantly, we kept
going and following the exact same
strategy. So, I have a boat and I love
going out on my boat. That's like my
therapy. That's what I like to do on my
free time. David's never been out of the
boat or even in Miami. I said, "You know
what? Let's go out." This is the first
time out on the boat. How is it? Good.
Where are your shorts?
>> Told me to wear pants.
>> Who told you to wear pants, bro?
>> I don't remember who it was, but
somebody told me to wear pants. Guy's
living the life.
>> He's living his best life, bro. Look at
this guy.
[Music]
for
it for baby.
>> And I think this was perfect because we
encountered somebody from the community
that had one of the craziest mindsets
and it honestly motivated me, motivated
David and it kept us going.
>> Guys, keep grinding, keep pushing, bro.
Don't ever give up. I promise you it's
not that hard. It's simple, right? But
it's it's a little bit complex cuz all
you got to do is do the same [__] every
day. That's the important part. That's
the hard part, right? Because when you
don't want to do it, it's hard to do it.
That's where discipline comes in. This
man ain't do all this [__] just because
he had the motivation, man. [__]
motivation. Do that [__] because you got
to lock in. You got to do it. Listen,
this is what say I always say, if you
don't lock in, you going to have to
clock in.
I like that. Yo, that yo yo, you
speaking some real [__]
>> It's facts. Because at the end of the
day, you do not want to die. You don't
want to be on your deathbed saying,
"Bro, what if I would have just gave it
a shot? What if I would have just been
like, "Fuck, let me just go all in."
Because at the end of the day, the same
people that's having opinions with you
now, they going to be in the same death
bed with you later, and they going to be
like, "Fuck, having the same thoughts.
What if I would have done it?" So, at
the end of the day, bro, just do you.
[__] do what you got to do
because listen,
the worst case is that you start at
square one regular working a regular
job. My job ain't that regular. But
listen, I'm blessed. I did uh I'm not
like Alex. I'm trying to get like Alex.
But listen, bro, we all going to get
there one day. Don't compare yourself.
Comparison is the thief of joy. Just be
grateful for where you at. Thank God
every day. You know what I'm saying? And
listen, if you got something you want to
work towards, keep working towards it.
Don't worry about it. Just keep working
towards that, bro. I promise you it's
going to work out because all you got to
do is believe in yourself. You know what
I'm saying? If you can't believe in
yourself, how you going to expect the
next man to believe in you? You know
what I'm saying? Most people don't even
believe in themselves. So, you can't do
that either. But other than that, y'all
have a great day. Much love vlog. Y'all
keep doing your thing. Alex, yo, you
already know, man. Keep doing your
thing. Camera man, I be peeping you,
too, man. Y'all be grinding, bro.
>> So, as we wrap up week one, we are ready
for war with week two. If the first week
was already kicking our ass, even though
we had great opportunities, we were not
going to let the market tick our ass on
week two. So, we came [__] ready.
>> Do you feel confident this week being
the co-pilot that majority of decisions
are going to be based off of
>> my person?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, for sure. 100%. Of course. I've
been studying. I've been seeing the last
week how it was. So, I think I'm ready
to take the leap. Sal was worried for
me, but I was ready to go. So, the start
off of week 2 honestly was pretty slow,
which was something that I didn't
expect. and we really didn't have
nothing other to do than just wait for
the market to give us the opportunity.
So, in the meantime, David has never
learned how to drift. I consider myself
a semi-professional drifter. So, I
decided to give him some lessons.
[Music]
Okay.
Go. Wait. One more.
[Music]
Heat.
[Applause]
Heat. Heat.
I dare to show some
[Music]
on the next market update. We actually
ended up taking a trade a little bit
before London session, I believe, or
into London session. But what I do
remember is that we had a side quest
mission probably of the year. So Ano is
a big Latin music artist in Latin
America and he happens to be one of my
close friends. He was doing a music
video here in Miami and he wanted a
professional drifter. What a coincidence
that I was just teaching somebody how to
do that earlier that day. I don't know
if this is signs. I don't know what it
is, but he wanted me there to go do some
donuts. And little did I know that this
is going to be a lot longer than I
thought. As of right now, we are yet to
take any new trades into the account. We
have missed some opportunities, but we
haven't executed one and we might
execute one in the next 30 minutes. Let
me break it down. So, starting off the
markets with Euro AUD. Currently, we are
creating a very, very strong left head
right shoulder. The daily time frame is
clearly having a reaction from this
level. Last time we were here, we had a
massive daily bearish engulfing
candlestick, which we entered on the
next day on the wick pullback retest and
then we caught the cells. We made a lot
of money here a while ago. And if you
notice, it's the exact same thing
happening here. Massive daily bearish
engulfing. And right now, it's
potentially creating that wick pullback.
4hour time frame head and shoulders. 1
hour time frame, we're already seeing
some type of a slowdown along with an
engulfing here. So, I'm going to wait
for a little bit more confirmation to
enter this trade. But this is exactly
where I'm going to look to enter this
trade. My stop loss will probably
somewhere around here. My take profit
somewhere around here. Trade update 1
a.m.
>> Yeah. 1 a.m. Right now we are up 1,600
bucks.
>> Say what?
>> Oh yeah.
>> 1600 bucks. Right now the Euro UD is
having a very strong push to the
downside. AUD CAD is having a double top
and USD JPY has officially broken it.
But not exactly what I want. So I'm
going to continue to hold this position.
So you guys ask me how do I stay up for
London? You [__] like this. We we shoot
music videos. That's That's how we stay
up.
>> You're going to be in the music video.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. They asked for me.
>> The J kid. Yeah.
[Music]
>> The next trade update, as I expected,
was at 4:00 in the morning and we were
still there. But I saw in the account
that we were up about $2,500. So, we
were up almost $5,000 on the account.
That was pretty cool to watch, but was
not ready what was going to happen next.
Diddy came back or tried to come back
once again. We were up in profit nearly
$3,000
and the market came back right into our
entry and even putting us into a little
bit of loss. So, stayed up all night for
a music video and uh got the biggest
biggest biggest blue balls by this
trade, potentially hitting take profit
and we had a complete reversal. Story of
our lives and yep, it happened again.
Yep, we got waked out again. Just at
this point, it's like if the market is
literally watching us, right? Am I crazy
for thinking that?
>> What happened, man? Why are you asking
me the questions? You're a
>> captain. You said you're the co-pilot.
>> Yeah.
>> Whatever I do, you're supposed to verify
and make sure I'm doing right. Right.
>> So, I'm going to ask myself and I'm
going to ask you.
>> Okay.
>> I don't know what happened, man.
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> Enter the trade. Enter the trade again
right now. Fix whatever we did wrong.
Fix it. Fix it. Fix it.
>> Didn't do [__] [__] man. We got margin
called right now once again. Oh, and
that was Matt.
>> Oh, yo, no way. Did Did the screen
break?
>> So, as another side quest mission, life
continues. Despite challenge or not,
despite take profit, march in Call of
Duty or not, I just got to do regular
stuff. So, had some situation going on
with the Bugatti and obviously it got
involved in an accident. decided to take
David there and show him. Probably his
first Bugatti ever. Not in the best
condition that I would wanted to show to
him, but it was the current situation of
the Bugatti.
>> And that could easily be the craziest
thing I've seen in my life. We're
talking about a $6 million car
completely smashed.
>> And shortly after that, I realized that
the market did try and wick us out. We
were never wrong about the trade. The
trade never hit our stop-loss. We ended
up just taking a small loss because of
the margin that we had in the account
and truthfully this was still a great
opportunity.
>> Same thing.
>> I know. I know.
>> Margin call.
>> Well, you seen you seen the patterns
here, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Kind of looking like me now, bro. But
yeah, we got margin called earlier today
and right now the trade is in profit.
So, like this is what I'm talking about.
Like we technically did not lose the
trade. We just got margin. like we're
right about the direction, right about
the entry, right about the stop loss.
Since we're just overexposing our
account, we basically got wiped out
>> and I was right once again. We were not
wrong. We simply got the loss because we
are overleveraging our account and fine
that is not the right thing to do. But I
am convinced that the market is watching
me at this point because it's crazy that
they try and take us out and as soon as
they take us out, they go straight to
take profit. Thankfully, we have learned
from our lessons previously. We've
turned losses into lessons and we've
held oursel accountable for whenever we
lose a trade. And I know if I'm not
wrong about the trade and I just tried
to get wicked out for the third or
fourth time that the trade is going to
continue going our direction. So, I
should go and hop back in. So, the
market did us. Wasn't super aggressive.
was very minor, a minor diddy, and we
managed to enter back into the trade and
then obviously be in profit, I think
north of $3,000, which was pretty cool.
And now on this market update, David and
I almost had a point of reflection. If
we would have taken every single trade
that we would have anticipated or that
we anticipated for the week ahead and we
did not get wicked out on those
positions, we would be north of 20 to
$30,000 by the halfway mark nearly of
week number two.
>> Right now, we're sitting at around
>> Oh, it's looking good. Decent about
$2,500 in profit. Balance is 38. So, if
we would have not lost the first trade,
>> don't even tell me that. Yeah. Like if
we do the sum of all this [__] we
shouldn't be losing. We'd be up so much
money right now.
>> Like not double, but like close to
double.
>> No, we'd probably be up almost double.
Like if we didn't lose the last margin
call.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
>> We would have just continue to hold.
Yeah, we would be up total of eight
lots. Yeah, we'd be up a little more.
>> And I was a little bit thirsty for that
trade to hit hard. I mean, if we took
every single trade that we analyzed, we
would have been at 20K already. But
seeing Alex so calm made me realize that
I have to level up my game. Trading with
a millionaire is not an easy task. And
there I felt the pressure of the ups and
downs. But I realized as well the
importance of the mental game in
trading. That's where I realized that
this is going to be a real mental
challenge. The market opportunities are
there. But it's the mindset of the
person executing those trades that is
going to either get us there or not. And
we were both having challenges at that
point because me getting David up to my
level of awareness was a challenge for
me and David catching up to speed at the
level that I wanted to was also a big
challenge. So we both had different
perspectives of everything. But we ended
up just focusing on what we had to and
coming out on top. Market update. It is
currently midnight right now. We are up
about $2,000 in the account.
So we're slowly cooking. This trade can
potentially be our last trade for the
week kind of. I don't know. I'm going to
definitely
>> So, you said you're saying that that
trade can take us to the 9,000.
>> Um, I don't know, man. I have to see how
the next hour candlestick closer, the
next 30 minutes. Based off of that, I'm
going to then determine if I close the
trade or not. And if I close the trade,
then we enter another trade.
>> Yeah, I was going to ask you if we're
going to just close that one and enter
another position or just
>> I mean, it really depends. All right.
So, let me show you guys. All right,
here we have Euro AUD and we've had a
massive push from this neckline to the
downside. Beautiful continuation shift
to the downside. Beautiful bearish push.
Even we had the news have the
retracement, retested this area and is
still having the push. But you guys have
to remember like this is a major counter
trend trade. We did the counter trend
trade up into this area because we have
the left head right shoulder. We're
retesting the neckline and the structure
where we can potentially now have the
higher high push. This is the first area
where this market can have the retest
before having the push to the upside.
So, we can't be greedy and expect for
this market just to continue going down
just because we predicted this one move
right here. And this right here is our
takeprofit, which is always a minimum of
a 1 to2 and we technically hit that. I
just stretch it out a little bit and put
a little bit low. So, I'm just going to
wait to see if it closes how I want it
to. I might hold a little bit more, but
I might just close and then enter buys
to the upside. I don't I need to see how
price action plays out for me to make a
decision here. Now, on this next market
update, I remember that it was sunrise,
6:00 in the morning, and David was, I
think, fasting for 2 days cuz he's was
really taking serious his weight loss.
And I said, "You know what, champ? I got
you. Let me monitor this trade tonight.
And if we get this certain opportunity,
we're going to scale in and enter this
position here." And that's exactly what
happened. I decided to stay up
throughout basically the whole entire
night. and uh ended up working out in
our favor very well because it put us up
on top of the challenge and we saw a lot
of market opportunities moving in London
lately. So, we decided to double down on
that session which ended up playing out
very well in our favor throughout the
whole entire challenge. What is going on
ladies and gentlemen? Market update. It
is currently 6:06 in the morning as you
guys can see to the top right hand
corner. Let me show you guys. We closed
out on the sells exactly how I
anticipated. 4hour time frame came into
this area. I'm already seeing how it's
going to close with a bullish pin bar.
I'm already seeing the 1 hour have the 1
hour engulfing. And as that's happening,
I said boom, we got to close it. Close
the trade. And then I basically broke
down earlier how I could anticipate this
trade to have a push to the upside. We
are taking a counter trend trade in this
move right here. Price could have a
reaction from the structure point. And
all I'm going to continue to do right
now is to hold. I might close this
position in the next 15 30 minutes. I'm
just waiting for I don't even know if I
want to wait for this candlestick to
close because I believe New York session
is just going to have the retracement
honestly. So I might just close now. All
right, I'm back. It's funny. I'm
literally talking to myself and you can
see how it's daytime now. Like I'm
literally just sitting here and I'm
watching the sun come up and I haven't
[__] slept anything. It's 6:22 in the
morning. So what like 15 20 minutes from
the last update? Last update was at
$4,000 and I'm literally seeing my
profits just like trickle away. I'm
literally seeing the technicals and I am
completely understanding that this is
going to reject this area exactly how I
said and that this market is literally
going to have now a higher low to then
have a new higher high. I should lock in
these profits before. So, I'm going to
close this live right now here with you
guys. So, it's literally projecting
exactly how I anticipated. [__] We
didn't stay at $6,000 in profit, bro. By
a [__] dollar, bro. [__] And the
rest of the week pretty much consisted
of just empty market updates of just the
market not giving us a lot of
opportunities. It was just update after
update after update. It was a week to us
be sitting on our hands. Even though
market was moving pretty quick, we
weren't really getting the opportunities
that we wanted. That met strategy. Now,
that's the importance of this account
flip aside from the risk management is
the strategy. We're not just taking any
trade from any break and retest or any
breakout. Like, we're following a strict
type of trade that we're looking to
enter every single time that the
patterns tend to repeat themselves
rather more times than not. And we just
simply didn't get that opportunity. So,
the boys at the end of the week, we
realized that we didn't hit the goal of
the week of 9,000. We were short by
about 3,000. And we decided to let off
some steam by playing some paintball.
And we all got smoked.
>> Respect. And I heard you so and so.
You're not a threat cuz I really know so
and so. They like my family. So they
will pretend that they cool to bust your
[__] chest. I'm getting my flow
like on my check. They see the number.
All of my haters feel one of two ways.
Really upset. They show some.
>> Now moving on to week number three. So,
our goal for this week is to be, I
think, a little bit over 18,000 in
profit. That's our very ambitious goal
that we're trying to hit for the week.
And I let David know that he has been
the co-pilot for the last two weeks. And
that now this week, he is going to be
the captain of the ship and I'm going to
be the co-pilot. That all of the lessons
that I have taught him in the last two
weeks, all of the questions that I've
answered of him, everything that we have
just gone through is all to this moment.
You're the captain now. It's time for
you to drive the ship and get us to
where we're supposed to go. Don't worry,
I'm right next to you. Any questions,
anything, feel free to ask me at any
point. Have no hesitation because this
is the ultimate point to test how good
my strategy is and how good I am of a
mentor teaching somebody else to execute
it in real time. Good evening. How y'all
doing? Welcome to week three, taking
$1,000 to $100,000. Now, usually I've
been the captain of the ship, but I'm
going to retire my chair for today. You
know what? for the week
>> for a week. A whole week
>> and you are going to be the captain of
this week.
>> So, the start off of the week was a
little bit slow. The market didn't
really give us any opportunities, but
that was shortly changed because we got
a decent opportunity on GBP NZD, which
was potentially going to take us to our
goal for the week, but wasn't looking as
confident as I thought.
>> Yeah, that's the face of somebody that
just got diddy. I mean, that
>> Oh, come on.
>> That was You always thinking about
Diddy, man. What's What's going on?
That's the face of somebody that just
entered a profitable trade. So please
break it down.
>> So basically the trade that we enter was
JVPN. I mean last week and all of these
past days we're looking for sales. Now
we basically broke over here the this
Irish structure and we had the retest
and a far from that gave us the 4hour
pimper confirmation. So basically we
entered now we entered as well based on
the 30 minute time frame because we had
this left head right shoulder as well as
this sh structure. So, we basically
anticipated the push.
>> This right here is literally the perfect
example of having a perfect shift to
structure at the area of interest and
it's literally lower high, lower low,
lower high, lower low, higher high,
shift to structure, retest, bullish
engulfing as it gets inverted head and
shoulders retesting it with the EMA
Picasso right here. The following trade
updates pretty much just consisted of us
watching GBPNZD go into profit come back
nearly 50% of what we were in profit and
was another one of those trades that we
just had to set and forget. Really had
no other choice. Now on this next update
is where things started to get real. We
have been at a 4 figure account for
pretty much the last 3 weeks and we have
officially just cracked the five figure
mark. As soon as I see five figures on
an account, things are getting real. I
know that we're a couple flips away from
completing the challenge. Five figure
mark is really the point you want to be
at to then start minimizing your risk to
about 50% 40%. In order for you to
actually be able to take those
high-risisk trades, but not blow the
account and then reset yourself back all
the way to the beginning and just waste
all that time. So, we have officially
hit the next threshold of having a five
figure account. And I wanted to withdraw
a 10K. Come on. 10K in in 3 weeks.
That's what I used to make in 6 months.
After some deep analyzing, we realized
that it made sense to just close the
trade at that point, get our five
figures. Our goal for the week was
18,000. We're a little bit shy of that,
but I rather secure our positioning at a
five figure account, and then we can
minimize our risk on the next trade and
then very easily and not be super
overexposed in the account, and we can
hit our goal of the 18,000 for the week.
So, that's what we did. We closed the
trade. So,
>> well, you got to give him the update.
What time is it? What's going on? Come
on, man. Come on, man.
>> Give him the update.
>> 32. So, basically, good morning,
everybody.
>> Good morning. Really early today,
Thursday, basically. Yeah,
>> it's 1:00 in the morning. Yeah, it's
almost 1:00 in the morning.
>> So, we closed the trade earlier around
this area over here. We have the alarm.
Uh, we were up like 6,000 if I'm not
mistaken. Look at this. Yeah, right at
that point we were probably up easily
total in the account probably 20 grand.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I know. I know.
>> And you want to know what sucks even
more? That the trade could have actually
hit our take profit. We could have been
north of $18,000 if we just continued to
set and forget. And we didn't. We
decided to take that energy into another
trade
and we lost. So the trade that was a
winning trade, we cut short and we
decided to then be aggressive and enter
another trade and then we lost. But to
my point, to be fair, we did not lose a
big significant amount in the account.
We lost enough where we were willing to
take that risk, but it didn't blow the
account. It just set us back just a
little bit. But if we would have hit our
take profit, we would have been at the
goal for the week.
Don't let's let's let me explain you
guys.
>> Trade update.
>> Lost the account. Lost the trade last
night.
>> No, hold on. Don't lost the account.
I'll be [__]
Basically, uh, we enter the trade around
this area over here. And as you guys can
see,
>> Yeah. you got wicked out.
>> Yeah.
>> How does it feel to get wicked out?
>> They can look.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the [__] Yo,
we took a nail. And to be honest, I lost
a lot of confidence. So, after wrapping
up week number three, we had to spice
things up a little bit because David
made a promise that if he did not hit
the goal for the week, he was going to
get a face tattoo. And he said that as a
joke. But little do people know is that
they don't take things lightly. And if
you say you're going to do something,
you kind of have to stick to your word.
And he was obviously not going to get a
face tattoo. So, we decided to spice
things up on week number four. And that
is if we don't hit the goal for the week
that David would have to shave his head.
And uh let's say that's why he looks
like that.
[Music]
I was really scared of losing my hair
and look at me now. And like I had
mentioned earlier, once you're basically
at the five figure account in the
account, which is where we are at this
point, things start to move very fast.
As soon as you enter a trade, you're
going to see the results double, triple,
and they're going to be a lot more
significant. And we had some crazy
market opportunities this week that had
big risk-to-reward ratio. And let's just
say that the setup for guest strategy
did not disappoint.
>> Good morning and a really good morning.
>> Yeah. So, we gotta do this trade update
quick because this [__] is moving fast,
bro. So, I I I'll explain it today, bro.
So, la last night we had the perfect
trade continuation of the What am I even
talking about? It's not a trade
continuation. It's the counter trend
trade. We literally had the lower high
that we were looking for last night. I
was telling David we should have entered
all the way up here because if this is
the liquidity grab has a quick
retracement and then we should enter up
here before it has the whole entire
move. But they wanted to wait for that
extra confirmation. We got that extra
confirmation last night and literally
all of last night has literally just
consisted of a quick minor pullback and
this morning straight push. So we have
surpassed our takeprofit point right
here. So if we look at right here, we
were just $40,000 in equity. Now we're
36. So we're we're gonna [__] bro. I
don't know if we should close or not
because look, let me explain. This is a
counter trend trade, right? And right
now on this countertrend trade, we've
already reached this point right here.
So, the fact that it's reached this
point, it's already going to potentially
have a reaction from here to head to the
upside. For example, break, retest, head
to the upside, right? This is the break,
retest from this area, continue head to
the upside. But this is such a massive
candlestick that it could just continue
going for the next 2 three days. So, I
would want to close right now, but I
want to leave you the decision.
>> Oh my god.
>> Okay, look, there's a couple things you
could do.
>> Okay. Okay. Let me know.
>> You can close two positions. Look at
that. We just lost $5,000.
>> What I'm saying like
>> you can close two positions, let one
run, or you can close all three. You can
close one, let two run. What do you want
to do?
>> What you What would you do? like being
completely honest. Will you will you let
one run?
I mean, do you think it's going to it's
going to like go back to draw down? Like
if we let the one Oh my god, bro. This
is such so crazy.
It's It's supposed to be doing this
here, right? It's supposed to have a
reaction from this area. Like this is
just what it's supposed to happen.
I mean, we have another opportunity on
CAD JPY that we missed. We avoided a
loss on GBPD.
We could close out GBPUSD because they
can [__] dude. We're just losing so
much money right now.
>> Let's close it. Let's close it. Go.
Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
>> Okay.
>> Wait. Should [__] bro. We just lost
$8,000, bro.
>> That's crazy.
>> Should we wait till it gets back to 35?
>> 35.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> [__] bro.
>> You think you think it will or at least
do like 26 again?
>> Well, let's not be greedy. Both
operations. Close it up. pushes.
>> It's technically her take. It's a done.
>> [__] bro. I know.
>> Damn, that's so crazy.
>> Market update. We closed out at 31,000.
>> Now, this market was moving so fast that
we saw $40,000 in profit on that market
and we could have literally closed it at
that point, but just to take a damn
video just to prove a point that we're
doing everything live, the market
reversed back to 30,000 in profit and
that's where we ended up closing the
trade. So, if we would just have closed
it when we should have, we would have
been up a lot more than what we would
have anticipated. But you know what?
Whatever keeps people happy, whatever
shows that we're actually doing this as
legitimately as we're possibly doing it.
Couple of market updates after that.
It's just pretty much analyzing the
market, sitting on our hands, and
waiting for the next solid opportunity
that was going to make sense for us to
risk 100% of the account, which could
pretty much be the trade that was going
to complete the challenge. So, we wanted
to make sure that we were being very
selective on that next trade that we
were taking. Patience is key at this
point. I get it. You just want a big
trade. You feel like a rock star. You
feel like you're invincible. But that's
really not how it goes. You need to
humble yourself and you need to make
sure that you're taking a trade for what
it is. And there's a lot of off camera
talk with David. There's a lot of behind
the scenes just kind of like oneon-one
me just molding David and be like,
"Brother, I get it. This is a lot of
money. This is cool." But you need to
normalize this money.
>> And because of the last trade, I started
getting ahead of myself. But Alex held
me down and put my feet on the earth
again.
>> You can't just think that you're the
[__] right now just because you made all
this money and that you're going to
predict the next move. That's how the
market takes it all away from you. You
need to be very humble, very stoic, and
pretend like the next trade has no
association to the last because it
doesn't. So, at this point in the
challenge, I pretty much see ourselves
passing it in the next week or two. And
I know a lot of people that were in the
challenge, like following the series
live, they really took advantage of
everything that we did in that series.
We literally shared before, during the
after every single trade and we were
hosting live streams in the middle of
the week and before the week even
started doing live updates, Q&As's on
the challenge. This way, there was
absolutely no excuse on why you can't
follow the journey and understand
exactly the type of trade and why I'm
looking to take it. Many people are
curious on why I take counter trend
trades a certain way. Many people are
curious why I hold trades a certain type
of way. And these live streams were very
educational and very beneficial to
anybody any type of experience you have
in the market. Now wrapping up for the
fourth week, we missed so many
opportunities which is normal in the
market at this point. I feel like we
actually missed more opportunities than
we entered. But you know what? That is
totally fine. And entering a trade that
doesn't meet the strategy to me is a
winning trade because it didn't meet it.
Has to meet the strategy for me to take
it. If it doesn't the trade, those
results that money to me never existed.
Doesn't have no association to me. And
later on into the fifth week, we have
another mistrade. I feel at this point
we have honestly missed over 10 trades
that have easily all of them
coincidentally given us a positive 1 to3
1 to4 risk-to-rewards and the ones that
we actually enter are giving us a 1 to2
1-2.5. Ask me why and I don't have the
answer. This is the beauty and the
mastery of the market and the
psychological execution at that point of
the mindset of the trader that just
somehow doesn't connect. It's the beauty
of the market. It is what it is. And all
of this led us to the grand finale, the
last trade, the holy grail, the
touchdown of the century or of the month
for us. Euro USD. What a way to take the
last trade on the challenge on the most
commonly traded pair in the globe, the
euro and the dollar. Now, what would you
expect when you hear both of these
currency pairs? You would expect low
fees, you would expect volatility, and
you would expect movement, right? That's
what you would expect when you hear this
market. Yeah, we actually got the
complete opposite. This market did
nothing for nearly three days and it
consolidated, went into draw down,
little bit of profit, draw down, profit,
draw down, profit for three days. But
obviously, I didn't know that was going
to happen. I thought since it was the
most traded pair in the whole entire
world that it would have the biggest
move. So, I decided to turn on a live
stream and not turn it off until we hit
that goal. And that was shorty lived. I
was not prepared to be on live stream
for even a couple of hours. I forgot
what that felt like. And on top of that,
our system wasn't having great
connection. We were trying to stream
outside of the house like I do stuff
outside of the house. Wasn't just going
to leave you guys stuck on the computer
board. And uh we ended up deciding to
turn off the live stream. And the trade
stayed in the exact same spot for the
next 48 hours. The market did nothing.
Had two massive daily dogeis just
consolidating.
But then on Friday, everything changed.
Euro USD after nearly three days and on
the last session essentially of the week
decided to break that level of support
and treat it as resistance and have a
massive daily dogey wickfill. Now, I'm
not going to lie. We entered another
impulsive entry on this trade due to the
fact that we're creating double daily
dogeis and we had the opportunity to add
a position. And this let us reach the
trade to not only more of our goal of
north of 100,000, but it was able to do
it in essentially after 2 hours, 3
hours. So, it consolidated for nearly 3
days. And in just two hours alone, ended
up having to move directly to our
take-profit point. Closed it live in
front of everybody, recorded it, screen
recorded, got the whole nine. And
David's reaction was just priceless.
>> Ghost.
Oh my god, bro. How does it feel to make
six figures? Obviously, I helped you
out, but how does it feel?
>> That much money is I've never seen that
much money on my life.
>> Like that this goes to your bank
account. How does that feel? That's just
crazy.
>> And I couldn't believe my eyes. Like, we
did it. We turned $1,000 to $100,000
with Alex. Mind you, $100,000 for me
will be working every single day, 16
hours a day for at least 5 years. And we
did it in just 5 weeks. And you know,
when Alexis came to Naples, I couldn't
imagine what was going to happen. And
the best part is that I'm a whole
different person. I have a better
physique and I have an ability that's
going to make me mai my parents and give
me a way better life and the most
important part is being surrounded or
having an environment that supports you
and having a mentor. So I want to say
that I'm really grateful for Alex and
for what he did for me in this 5 weeks
and you know how it is guys whenever in
doubt just set and forget. Now this was
not my first time doing an account flip.
I've done many account flips. I'm known
for taking $100 into a million that took
me little bit about a year after trial
and error. I've done a lot of stuff just
personally. I've done a lot of stuff
with my friends. But there was something
different about this challenge about
helping a stranger literally know very
little trading to then how to properly
do an account flip. There's something
about seeing the body transformation of
somebody that comes to my house
overweight and they have a complete
physical change. The routine, the
habits, their mindset. Like it's crazy
how in five weeks I completely changed
the spectrum of a complete stranger's
life. There's people out there that have
been following the challenge for the
whole entire 5 weeks and at the end of
the challenge they're in the exact same
position. Nothing changed in their
lives. David came in as one person and
left as another in just 5 weeks. 5 weeks
it changed his whole entire ecosystem.
changed his whole entire existence for
his last 20 years of life in just five
weeks. And that to me was very powerful.
That to me was honestly a great
experience. And I am truthfully
motivated to continue to do things like
this. Just showing you guys if you just
simply lock in are around the right
people and stay doing the exact same
thing over and over and over again.
Learn from your losses, it is inevitable
that you succeed. And this was the
perfect example. This was a great
experience and I hope to do something
like this again soon. And one of the
promises that I set for myself is if I
successfully complete this G challenge,
which is what we called, that I was
going to open this up to other people
because I almost used David as a guinea
pig. I wanted to see if this is a proven
concept and that it works. And let me
tell you something, it [__] works.
So, I am now opening up some spots to be
parts of what is named the G-Club, where
I'm going to have other people have the
same opportunity that David, where you
can follow the exact same road map and
replicate the exact same blueprint that
I created for him, so you can do a
journey just like his. Some people here
in person, some people remote online.
down below. I'm going to leave a link
for you in the description below so you
can get access to a call, a very private
exclusive call where I'm going to break
down how you can join the G- Club and if
you even qualify. Truthfully, this is my
most ambitious and most latest updated
strategy program I've done to this date.
And I'm very excited for this next
journey. And over these last 5 weeks,
there was a lot of people following the
challenge. But when it comes to my
community, there's people that were
asking me direct questions of some trade
ideas. I hopped in random Zoom calls
throughout the week. And this is the
benefits of the center forget strategy.
With or without the challenge, you're
able to access me and ask me any
questions at any given points once
you're inside of the community along
with these weekly calls that I would
host. And that is something that I did
publicly for free during the challenge
just to prove a point and show people
what it's about and showcase it. But now
that the challenge is over, I no longer
do it publicly and I only do it for my
community. So if you want to know more
about the set and forget community,
click the link in description down below
so you can see how students are having
account flips very similar to David by
following my set and forget strategy.
All I can say is David is not the only
one following the strategy and having
results with it. So if you want to know
more about what the seven forget
strategy is about, click the link in
description below. It's a video for that
explains it for you. And this Sunday we
have some crazy markets pulling up
exactly like the last ones that we just
broke down. So, with that being said,
ladies and gentlemen, thank you very
much for watching this video all the way
to the end. Make sure to hit that like
and subscribe button if you guys enjoyed
this video. You haven't seen any of our
other videos in the channel, make sure
to check them out. There's so much value
on my channel that you have no idea how
undervalued it is and how much you can
learn from it. It is all completely for
free. I invite you to go watch them.
Cost you nothing. You can learn a lot
from it. With that being said, thank you
very much for watching this video. See
you guys on the next one.
>> So, this morning we got a little
surprise for Mr. Alex G. Uh, I don't
know if you can focus it up over here.
Freshly done. He has no idea about it.
So, we're going to call him and see his
reaction.
>> So,
we want to hit the positively last week
of the challenge. So I wanted to do
something and to let you know that in
case we complete it or in case we don't
I will be truly grateful for the rest of
my life cuz just not about the money the
experience that I've had and the
learning progress and I mean what I told
you always that you expanding my mind is
always going to be there you know so I
wanted to do something again the same
way the same the same way that I'm
telling you they're going to stay with
me for the rest of my life to have
something that's going to stay with me
visible for the rest of my
What do you think it is?
>> I know.
>> You did it.
>> No.
Hey, [__] savage, bro.
>> Oh my god. Why don't you Why don't you
do it higher, bro?
>> Why?